https://www.carpeople.com/privacy-policy/

News
We respect your privacy!
What personally identifiable information is collected on this site?Visitors may supply personally identifiable information (such as name, address or telephone numbers) for various purposes on this site. These purposes include registering to receive e-mail newsletters, requesting further information about our services, or signing up with us to use our service. Car People does not collect personal information from you unless you provide it to us. This means that you can visit our site without telling us who you are or revealing any personally identifiable information about yourself.How is it used?When you supply information about yourself for a specific purpose, we use the information for only that purpose. If it is to receive our newsletter then that is the only use we will have for that specific information. If you sign up with us to use our services then the information you give us is Confidential and will not be released unless we have your permission.SecurityPersonally identifiable information is stored on our in office data base and is not publicly accessible. Further, personally identifiable information is only accessed by Car People employees on a “need to know” basis. All Car People employees are trained and thoroughly aware of the importance of securing this information. Car People meets or exceeds all industry standards for the protection of personally identifiable information.Choice/Opt-outIf you have registered to receive e-mail communications from us and later change your mind, you may contact us to have your name removed from our distribution lists.Correct/UpdateIf you would like to verify the data we have received from you or to make corrections to it, you may contact us directly at the e-mail and mail addresses provided above.LinksThis site may contain links to other Web sites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are entering another site. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of these linked sites as their privacy policy may differ from ours.E-mail LinksWe use e-mail links located on this site to allow you to contact us directly via e-mail. We use the information provided in your e-mail to respond to your questions or comments. We may also store your comments for future reference. Your personal information is only shared with third parties with your explicit permission.Legal DisclaimerWe may disclose personal information when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary in order to conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on us.For more informationIf you have any questions, concerns or comments, please e-mail info@carpeople.com
Car People Agency
© 2020 Car People Agency.
